Address: 1141 Spring Creek Rd.

Phone: (318) 245-9708 Email: knf010@latech.edu

Kennedy North Ford

Summary

Enthusiastic and dedicated student with a desire to learn and grow through every work experience that they are able to ascertain. Willing to do any and every task that is required of them, and almost overly motivated to achieve the very best result possible. Everything that they will do will be done to the best of their abilities and with the greatest amount of excellence possible.

Work History

MidSouth Pecan, Ruston, LA - Multipurpose worker

Sept. 2019 - Nov. 2020

- Cleaned, packaged, and stocked product
- Worked with shipping product to clients around the US
- Monitored heavy machinery

LaTech Computing Center Help Desk, Ruston, LA - IT associate

Sept. 2021 - Present

- Worked to help LaTech students & faculty troubleshoot their IT issues in person.
- Answered phone calls and assisted customers remotely.

EDUCATION

Union Christian Academy, Farmerville, LA — High School

Sept. 2017 - May 2019

Homeschooled through the 10th grade, and then decided to transfer to a private institution to complete a high school education as well as to complete 30+ hours of dual-enrollment credit. Finished school and graduated with a 3.9 GPA (on a 4.0 scale)

Louisiana Tech University | Ruston, LA — Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Sept. 2019 - Current

Began an education in the science of computing having learned three programming languages with an intermediate-adept skill level thus far (Python, Java, and C) as well as a couple other languages on a basic level (Bash, Assembly)